Scott Foster

 $3310\ Stardust\ Dr,\ Austin,\ 78757,\ United\ States,\ 773-910-8803,\ saf0911@gmail.com$

SOCIAL PROFILES	website www.scottfoster.work			
PROFILE	Project Manager with technical background and experience in managing international teams of web developers. Initiating planning and developing methods to increase efficiency of team members. Communicating clear goals to increase productivity and decrease costs.			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Jan 2018 – Jun 2018	Project Manager Independent Contractor, Meissner Consulting LLC		Meissner	Austin
	Managed a global team of 4 developers in 3 different countries Ensured product launch date was met pulling together a fragmented development team Used scrum and agile methods to ensure maximum efficiency of all team members involved Wrote a testing platform to ensure the site was functioning correctly at all times Tested the site manually in development for quality assurance			
May 2005 – Jul 2006	Personal Banker, UMB Bank			Kansas City
	Built customer relationships managing hundreds of accounts 4 million dollars Exceeded sales goals by 10% adding significant revenue streams every month Met federal and organizational guidelines for securing personal information			
2004 – 2005	Store Manager, Petro-Mart			Columbia MO
	Enacted store reorganization for more efficient work flow decreasing time to complete stocking and cleaning time decreasing employee costs by 12%			
	Created uniform ordering system to reduce stock increasing cash avalability			
1998 – 2004	Team Trainer/ Manager, QuikTrip			Kansas City
	Trained part time employees ensuring they met the goals and requirements of the job description Managed teams of up to 12 employees meeting or exceeding the daily work assignments and ensuriaccurate accounting for each shift. Maintained and ordered inventory for stores with millions in sales each month			
EDUCATION				
Sep 2007 – Dec 2008	Kendall College, Culinary Arts A.A.			Austin
Aug 2003 – Jun 2005	Columbia College, Bachelors Business Management			Columbia MO
COURSES				
Oct 2016 – Jul 2017	Full Stack Web development, Austin Coding Academy			
SKILLS	Web Development	Beginner	Problem Solving	Experienced
	Team Building	Experienced	Relationship Building	Expert